Inventory of the Dean of the College Records, 1971 - 1997
Dean of the College Records, 1971 - 1997
- Series 2: Dean of the College Files
  - Institutional Research
    - IR [Institutional Research]: Task Force on Info. Access, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - PreMedical Education, Consortium for the study of (IR) c. 1982, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - IR: Recruitment, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - IR: Healy Study, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - IR: Senior Survey CPC, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - IR: Senior Survey ’87, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - IR: Values, Academic Qualifications, Probable Majors and Career Plans, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - IR: Progress Toward Graduation, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - IR: Career Planning, c. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - IR: Oberlin Science Conference, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - IR: 1973, 1974, 1977, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - IR: 1985 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Institutional Rights Review Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Inter Fraternity Council (IFC), 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Board of House Presidents, 1983-1985, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - International Baccalaureate, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Bail and Legal Aid Fund, 1975-1977, 1980, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Minutes Legal Defense and Bail Fund 1-76, 1976, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - International Studies, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Little Three 6/90, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Levy-Spira Fund, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Learning Disabilities, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Luce Scholars, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Marc Program, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Math Department, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ronald McNair Program (2 folders), 1984, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
  - IPEDS [Integrated Post-Secondary Education Data System], 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Intro Science Courses, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Majority Students, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - WesJack, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Jews and Judaism at Wesleyan, 1987, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Jobs for Youth Community Services, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Holidays, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Joint Major, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - United States: Department of Justice, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Kosher Kitchen, 1986-1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Latino Alumni Council, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Latino Presence at Wesleyan, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Learning Skills, Inc. 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Fraternities
    - VP and Sec. of Fraternities General, 1987, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - VP and Sec. of Fraternities General, 1991-1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - VP and Sec. of Fraternities General, Alpha Delta Phi, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Beta Theta Pi, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - VP and Sec. of Fraternities General, Beta Theta Pi, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - VP and Sec. of Fraternities, Chi Psi, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - VP and Sec. of Fraternities, Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - VP and Sec. of Fraternities, Psi Upsilon, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Project 3000 by 2000, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Freeman Asian Scholars Program, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Upward Bound
    - Upward Bound, 1991-1996 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Upward Bound ConnCap, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Upward Bound Excel Program, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Upward Bound Grants Award, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Upward Bound Program Expansion, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Wesleyan Policies
    - Blue Book Changes, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Computer Use Policies, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Party Policy, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Poster Policy, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - ROTC, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Speech Codes, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Transportation policy, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Series 3: Restricted Materials